When I first did It Kills Me, I remember going into record labels and people saying,
nobody wants to hear anyone sing that well.
What?
Uh-huh.
I was told I sang.
Wait, nobody wants to hear anyone sing that well?
Right now in that time of music.
Well, who was out at that time of music?
I mean, like, and it's no shade to anyone else.
Like, I mean, Ashanti was the huge pop R&B artist of that time.
And like, the music was more hip hop driven.
It was more pop driven.
Where did Bridges go?
They are gone.
Can we build a bridge to Bridges?
Hello.
That's a podcast.
I really missed the bridge.
The bridge was everything.
A key change.
A moment.
Modulation.
It was, you know, it was a thing.
And so I remember going into meetings and people being like, you're beautiful.
You're young.
Like, nobody wants to hear you sing that well or speak that well.